你父母的情况怎么样了
Hey, how are things going with your parents?
不太好  他们请了离婚律师
Not great. They hired divorce attorneys.
说到律师
You know, speaking of attorneys,
如果哪天我需要请律师
if I ever needed a lawyer,
我绝对不会请女浩克
I would not hire She-Hulk.
绿巨人浩克的表妹  有弱化版的绿巨人变身能力
常为超级英雄们打官司
其实呢  你这次跟主题很接近了
You know what? That was almost on topic.
所以我要说"点赞哦  谢尔顿"
I'm gonna say, "Good job, Sheldon."
等等  女浩克是个律师吗
Wait, She-Hulk's a lawyer?
是啊  她在纽约一家律师事务所做事
Yeah, she works at a law firm in New York.
是的  但是她是所里唯一的怪物
Yes, but she's the only monster at the firm.
我说了别传出去啊
Between you, me and the wall,
我觉得她是因为平权法案才被请的怪物
I think she's an affirmative action hire.
为防止对肤色  宗教  性别  民族出身有所歧视
在就业  教育等方面给予优待而达到平等的措施
总而言之  我爸会来找我
Anyway, Dad's gonna be here in town,
所以我今年没办法替大家办圣诞晚宴了
so I won't be able to do Christmas dinner this year.
如果今年你没办法主办圣诞晚宴
If you're not up to hosting Christmas dinner,
我很乐意来做啊
I'm happy to do it.
你还可以带你父亲一起来
You can even bring your father.
那真是太好了
That would be nice.
我一直都想过一次传统维多利亚式圣诞
I've always wanted to do a traditional Victorian Christmas.
玩会客厅游戏  吃圣诞烤鹅与果干布丁
Parlor games, goose and figgy pudding...
当年家里有"会客厅"的中上阶层家庭的娱乐活动
圣诞烤鹅与广式脆皮烧鹅类似
英式布丁
English pudding.
英式布丁常是蛋糕状的甜点
而不是美式的偏果冻状布丁
本来满心期待有"布丁"吃
Y-You get yourself all excited for pudding,
结果是英式的破葡萄干蛋糕
and here comes a cake with raisins in it.
我不去
I'm not going.
你就得来
You're going.
我跟你什么仇什么怨啊
Why do you hate me?
我跟你无冤无仇
I don't hate you.
我爱你
I love you.
你把它称之为爱也行
Well, you call it love,
但里面还是有一堆葡萄干
but it has a lot of raisins in it.
艾米  让这几个家伙对主题晚餐有兴趣
Amy, good luck getting these guys excited
简直比登天还难
about a dinner with a theme.
我的汤姆·汉克斯感恩节就因为没人捧场而放弃
I gave up when no one cared about my Tom Hanks-giving.
我觉得维多利亚式圣诞很不错啊
I think a Victorian Christmas sounds nice.
-同意  -我也觉得
- I agree. - Me, too.
你们这群混蛋
You guys suck!
你知道在无尘室里工作最棒的是什么吗
You know the best part of working in the clean room?
不会过敏
No allergies.
你看
Check it out.
鼻子太通  一下吸进的氧气有点多
Oh, that-that... that's a lot of oxygen.
我们该去艾米家了
We should get going to Amy's.
你能相信曾几何时
Can you believe there was a time
人类得靠着
when we would have needed an array
巨大的切伦科夫望远镜阵列  来探测宇宙射线粒子
of giant Cherenkov telescopes to detect cosmic particles?
而如今我们自己就可以构建多线探测器
And here we are building our own multi-wire detector
简直霸气到炸啊
like a couple of badasses.
是啊  如果我们还单身
I know. If we were still single,
都可以在女人堆里打滚了
we'd be tripping over all that booty.
女人的确喜欢男人打扮得像个厨房垃圾袋
Ladies do love a man dressed like a kitchen garbage bag.
惨了
Oh, no.
这鸽子是怎么飞进来的
How the hell did a pigeon get in here?
-你关了外门对吧  -我以为你关了
- You shut the loading doors, right? - I thought you did.
你知道这有多严重吗
Do you know what a disaster this is?!
你是指因为这无尘室应该是要一尘不染
You mean 'cause this room isn't supposed to have dust in it,
而我们放了一只会飞的拉屎机进来吗
and we just let in a flying crap machine?!
我们该怎么办  该打电话叫人来吗
What do we do? Should we call someone?
告诉人家我们把所有设备都污染了吗
And tell them that we compromised all the equipment?
赶紧趁没人发现前把它赶出去
Let's just get it out of here before anyone knows.
好吧  我们该怎么抓它呢
Okay, how do we catch it?
要不我们把所有灯关掉
Well, what if we turn off all the lights
只留下一盏灯  它就会飞过来
except for one, and it'll come to it.
它又不是飞蛾
It's not a moth!
别吼我
Don't yell at me.
你越吼我  我越想不出什么好主意
You're not gonna get any good ideas out of me if you're yelling.
所以如果我保持平静
Okay, so if I remain calm,
我就能听到更多像"关灯"这样的绝妙大计吗
I'll get more gems like, "Turn off the lights"?!
这下好了  我们反目成仇
Great, we're turning on each other.
正中了这只鸟的下怀
That's just what the bird wants us to do!
库萨帕里医生  飞了很久吧
So, Dr. Koothrappali, long flight?
-足足20小时  -很辛苦吧
- 20 hours. - Oh, that's rough.
完全不会
Not at all.
不用跟妻子一起飞这种跨大陆航班
Did you know that when you fly transcontinental without your wife,
我也不用祈祷飞机赶紧坠机
you don't pray for the plane to crash?
我们能聊点别的吗
Can you please talk about anything else?
抱歉  原谅我
Forgive me.
你和莱纳德如何了
How are you and Leonard?
很好啊  一切都很好
Oh, great. Everything's good.
-我发现你们好像订婚了  -是啊
- I see you got engaged. - Yes, we did.
让我告诉你个故事
Let me tell you a story.
爸
Dad!
抱歉
Sorry.
我相信你们不会日渐憎恨彼此
I'm sure you won't grow to hate each other.
莱纳德  怎么啦
Hey, Leonard. What's up?
什么  怎么会这样
What? How did that happen?
好吧  我尽快到
Yeah, okay. I'll be there as soon as I can.
抱歉我得去一下大学
Sorry. I have to run to the university.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们的实验出了点问题
There's been a problem with our experiment.
有只鸟飞进了无尘室
A bird got into the clean room.
需要我去帮忙吗
You want me to come?
不用  你刚坐了这么长时间飞机
Uh, no. You had a long flight.
你就待着放松休息吧
You stay here and relax.
"放松"  你说得倒轻巧
"Relax." Easy for you to say.
你妈"清"空的又不是你的银行账户
Your mother isn't cleaning out your bank account.
40年来  这女人从未"清"理过任何东西
40 years, the woman never cleaned a thing.
你要把他丢在这里吗
You're just gonna leave him here?
-他还好意思让我放松  -是的  再见
- "Relax," He says. - Yup. Bye.
* 圣诞老人来了  圣诞老人来了 *
* Here comes Santa Claus, here comes Santa Claus *
* 正沿着圣诞老人道而来 *
* Right down Santa Claus Lane *
* 凶婆娘和闪电  与其它驯鹿们 *
* Vixen and Blitzen and all his reindeer *
圣诞老人一共有九只驯鹿  鲁道夫  猛冲
跳舞  欢腾  凶婆娘  雷  闪电  丘比特  彗星
* 卖力拉着缰绳 *
* Pulling on the reins... *
谢谢你能载我
Yeah, I appreciate the ride...
* 铃声叮当  孩子欢唱 *
* Bells are ringing, children singing *
* 一切快乐又光明 *
* All is merry and bright *
* 挂上你的圣诞袜  说出你的祷告词 *
* So hang your stockings and say your prayers *
* 只因今晚圣诞老人要到来 *
'Cause Santa Claus is coming tonight...
你干嘛关掉它
Why'd you turn it off?
因为在过去的十分钟里  《圣诞老人进城了》
Because in the last ten minutes, Santa came to town,
《我看见妈妈亲吻圣诞老人》
kissed Mommy
然后《奶奶被驯鹿撞死了》
and ran Grandma over with a reindeer.
我有个酒鬼叔叔也会做这三件事啊
I had a drunk uncle who did all those things.
怎么没人唱歌歌颂他呢
Nobody sings songs about him.
如果你把圣诞老人看做是超级英雄
Maybe you'd like it more if you thought of Santa as a superhero
有给孩子们带来欢乐的超能力  你会喜欢点
and his power is bringing joy to children.
我叔叔也这样啊  结果被指控了
My uncle was accused of that, too.
结果在俄州那是合法的
It turned out to be legal in Oklahoma.
好吧  换个话题
Okay, new subject.
我们聊聊礼物吧
Let's talk about presents.
你要送艾米什么呀
What did you get Amy?
我们不会互送礼物
Oh, we're not exchanging gifts.
拜托  谢尔顿  送礼物给女朋友是一定要的啊
Come on, Sheldon, you have to get her something.
凭什么
Why should I?
她明知道我不喜欢圣诞节
She knows that I don't like Christmas,
可是每一年都强迫我一起庆祝
and yet, every year, she forces me to celebrate it.
不光是这次逼我参加白痴的圣诞晚餐
Not only am I going to this foolish dinner against my will.
之前在圣诞树卖场那  有一个槲寄生
At the Christmas tree lot, there was mistletoe,
她居然当众亲了我
and she kissed me under it in public.
我们就像墨西哥性爱秀的表演者
Like we were the stars of a Tijuana sex show.
她只是对节日感到兴奋而已啦
She's just excited about the holidays.
是啊  而她完全不顾及我的感受
Yes, and she's not taking my feelings into account at all.
或许是时候给她点教训了
Maybe it's time I teach her a lesson.
怎么做
How?
一定要给她下点狠药
It'd have to be something heinous,
让她生不如死  就像她害我的那样
something that makes her as miserable as she's making me.
我想到了
Oh, I've got it.
这主意太好了
This is good.
是什么
What?
我要送她一份礼物
I'm going to buy her a present.
好吧  你得好好给我讲解一下
Yeah, you're gonna have to walk me through that.
礼品馈赠隐含了一种无形的社会契约
With gift-giving, there's an implied social contract.
如果我今晚带着礼物去她家
If I show up tonight with a present,
而她却没有为我准备礼物
and she doesn't have one for me,
那她就会内疚
she'll feel terrible.
然后你们俩都不开心
Then you're both sad?
是的
Yes.
或许她会内疚到
Maybe she'll feel so guilty,
永远都不想跟我一起庆祝节日
she'll never make me celebrate the holidays again.
所以你的邪恶阴谋是送你女朋友一份礼物吗
So your evil plot here is to buy your girlfriend a present?
没错
That's right.
所以别惹我  否则小爷也会赐你点"礼物"
So stay on my good side, or I'll get you a little something, too.
好  计划是这样
Okay, here's the plan.
我把食物放进袋子里
I'm gonna put the food in the bag,
一旦鸽子飞进去吃  我们就赶紧把口封死
and when he lands in the bag to eat it, we close it up.
一根肉条吗
A Slim Jim?
只有这个了  保证管用
It's all I could find. It'll work.
屁咧
Sure.
除非它嗑药了  或者它是卡车司机
If the pigeon's stoned or a trucker.
好吧  那你的计划是什么
Okay, well, what's your plan?
我之前不是说了吗
I told you my plan.
打给物业管理处  找人帮忙啊
Let's call Building Services and get help.
承认我们污染了无尘室吗
And admit that we contaminated the clean room?
不  是承认你污染了无尘室
No, admit that you contaminated the clean room.
为什么你总认为责任在我
Why do you keep assuming it was me?
因为你总犯这样的错误
Because you do this kind of thing all the time,
还会试图掩盖事实
and then you try to cover it up.
比如说
Like when?
比如说你把火星漫游者玩坏
What about when you flipped the Mars Rover,
弄丢了库萨帕里的狗
or lost Koothrappali's dog,
差点开别人的车带着别人的娃走了
or almost drove off with that baby?
重申一遍  那车跟我的车很像  而且那娃没哭
Again, it looked like my car, and the baby didn't even cry
是后来他妈用钥匙打我才吓哭的
until his mother punched me with her keys.
行  你想把肉条放垃圾袋里就放呗
Fine, put the Slim Jim in the garbage bag.
你能不能讲话不这么秀优越感
Well, what if you said it without sounding so condescending?
我尽量  但你的计划里有
I can try, but your plan has the words
"垃圾袋"和"肉条"这两个词
"Garbage bag" and "Slim Jim" in it!
什么情况
Hey, what's going on?
有一个天才想用一个垃圾袋
Genius here wants to catch a bird
和一根肉条抓住一只鸟
with a garbage bag and a Slim Jim.
真应该先放进袋子里
Should have put it in the bag first.
希望你别介意我多嘴
So, if you don't mind me asking,
你认为你会开始跟其他人约会吗
do you think you might start dating again?
现在说这个还太早吧
It's much too soon for that.
怎么了  要给我介绍对象吗
Why? Do you know someone?
没有啦  但如果我和莱纳德闹掰了
No, but if things don't work out with me and Leonard,
我会打给你的
I'll give you a call.
等等  你会经常大聊特聊《星际迷航》吗
Wait. How much do you talk about Star Trek?
好啦  我们维多利亚式派对开始啦
Okay, let's get this Victorian party started.
我做了些研究
I've done some research
找了几个我们可以玩的会客厅游戏
about some traditional parlor games we can play.
比如什么
Like what?
有一个有趣的游戏叫"羊毛球"
Well, there's a fun one called Ball of Wool.
你拿一个羊毛球
You take a ball of wool,
放在桌子的正中间
and you put it right in the center of the table.
然后让桌子两端的人
Then people sit on opposite sides of the table
来回吹毛球
and try to blow the wool off.
抱歉  她也有男友了
Sorry. She's taken, too.
你知道我觉得你问题在哪吗
You know what I think your problem is?
你嫉妒
You're jealous
因为你曾经是我最好的朋友
because you and I used to be best friends
现在库萨帕里插进来了
until Koothrappali came along.
于是你终于找到可以任你摆布的人了
And you found somebody you could push around?
-你别掺合  -好的
- Stay out of this. - Okay.
也许拉杰之所以能成为我最好的朋友
You know, maybe I'm best friends with Raj
是因为他不会觉得自己比我聪明
because he doesn't think he's smarter than me.
-其实...  -我说你别掺合
- Actually... - I said, stay out of it!
别别  拉杰你说  你刚刚想说什么
N-No. No, Raj, go ahead, say what you were gonna say.
我只想说
All I'm gonna say is
你们别再吵了
you guys need to stop this right now.
我父母闹矛盾已经够糟了
It-It's bad enough that my parents are fighting,
现在还要听你俩吵架
now I have to hear the two of you?
谁在乎谁更聪明啊
And who cares who's smarter?
谁管是莱纳德还是我  还是...
If it's Leonard or me or...
算了  大过节的  霍华德最聪明吧
you know, it's Christmas, let's say it's Howard.
既然你那么聪明  你把鸟赶出去啊
Well, if you're so smart, you get the bird out.
不  是你放进来的
No, you're the one who let him in.
你怎么知道不是莱纳德
How do you know it wasn't Leonard?
得了吧
Come on.
那件毛衣怎么样
What about that sweater?
不行  不够好
No, it's not good enough.
必须要完美
It has to be perfect.
我觉得华仔送我最棒的礼物是一份
I think the nicest gifts I've got from Howie
体现了他有多了解我的礼物
show how well he knows me.
我想想  我了解艾米什么
Let's see, what do I know about Amy?
她热爱中世纪文学  最欣赏乔叟
She loves medieval literature; Chaucer's her favorite.
杰弗雷·乔叟  英国文学之父
被公认为中世纪最伟大的英国诗人
在看法国老电影时  她的眼睛会变星星眼
And her eyes sparkle when she watches old French movies.
我爱看她会随着听到的竖琴声舞动手指
I enjoy how harp music causes her fingers to dance
仿佛一同弹奏
as if she's playing along.
你真的很爱她
Wow, you really do love her.
是呀
I do.
我们赶紧来找
Now, let's find the kind of gift
让她无地自容又自惭形秽的礼物吧
that makes her feel small and worthless.
你赢啦
You won!
一点胜利的喜悦都没有  对吧
Certainly doesn't feel like it, does it?
我老婆以前总喜欢办这种主题派对
You know, my wife used to throw theme parties like this all the time.
拉杰大概就是从那学的吧
Oh, I guess that's where Raj gets it from.
他小时候
Well, he and his mother
总是和他妈妈待在一起
spent a lot of time together when he was young.
我一直在忙工作
I was always working.
拉杰现在交往的医生也是经常忙工作
Hey, you know, Raj is dating a doctor who works a lot.
他和他妈都喜欢这型的
Him and his mom have a type.
你...不觉得好笑吗
You g... Y-You got to laugh at that, right?
不好笑  好吧
No? All right.
好吧  你听我理解得对不对
All right, let me see if I've got this straight.
用一张你坐在我腿上的照片
A picture of you on my lap
来惩罚你女友
is a way to punish your girlfriend
逼你过圣诞节
for making you celebrate Christmas?
正确
Correct.
圣诞老人觉得有你这种男友已经够受罪了
Santa thinks dating you may be punishment enough.
这话不无道理
There's an argument for that.
但我得确保她一定受到惩罚
But I want to make sure.
微笑
Smile.
呵呵呵
Ho, ho, ho!
好的  数到三
Okay. On the count of three,
我会用灭火器把它喷下来
I'll shoot the fire extinguisher and get him airborne.
霍华德你挥毯子把它逼向出口
Howard, you wave the blanket and guide him towards the exit.
拉杰你把门帘掀开让它可以飞出去
Raj, you hold open the curtain so he can fly out.
你确定我这样的傻蛋可以应付
Are you sure a dummy like me can handle something
毯子这么复杂的东西吗
as complicated as a blanket?
你想负责灭火器吗
Do you want the fire extinguisher?
-想  我想  -好
- Yeah, I do. - Great.
给你
Here you go.
好
Okay.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
你得先把安全针拔出来
Uh, you have to take the pin out.
现在怀念毯子了吧
You miss the blanket now, don't you?
数到三
On three.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
你干了什么
What did you do?
这是意外
It was an accident.
天啊  我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
别紧张  不是你的错
Relax, it wasn't your fault.
它可能只是吓呆了
Uh, maybe it's just stunned.
兄弟  呼吸都没了
Dude, I-it's not breathing.
不是吧  我杀了它
Oh, no. I killed it.
别又来啊
Oh, not again.
你说"又"是什么意思
What do you mean, not again?
在我十岁那年
When I was ten,
我在后院玩  然后...
I was playing in my backyard and...
坐到了一只冠蓝鸦上
sat on a blue jay.
我想用电击把它救活
I mean, I tried to bring it back to life with electricity,
但它...
but it just...
着火了
caught on fire.
最糟糕的是闻起来非常美味
The worst part was it smelled delicious.
两位  我找到一篇文章
Uh, guys, I found an article here
上面说心肺复苏可适用于鸟类
that says you can do CPR on birds.
太好了  你做啊
Great! Do it!
我才不去  你杀的  你负责
I'm not doing it. You killed him, you do it.
-我来  -不行
- I'll do it. - No.
得让我来
I need to do it.
这是我的责任
This is on me.
好
Okay.
"以嘴覆盖于喙  轻轻胸部挤压"
"Mouth over beak and light chest compressions."
别吹得太狠了
Don't blow too hard.
你把它吹炸了  我会吐的
If you pop him, I will vomit.
有发现吗
Anything?
我尝到好浓的肉条味
I am tasting a lot of Slim Jim.
等等   它的翅膀动了
Wait, wait, his wing moved!
它眨眼睛了  它活过来了
Oh, he blinked his eyes! He's alive!
这真是圣诞节奇迹啊
It's a Christmas miracle!
对我来说是光明节奇迹  不过圣诞节也不错
I might argue a Hanukkah miracle, but I'll take it.
来吧小家伙  我们放你出去  把帘子拉开
Come on, little guy, let's get you outside. Get the curtain.
有人真应该去关上外门
Someone should really close that loading door.
事情只能这样了
Well, that's that.
这个房间已经被污染了
The room's compromised.
所有的滤网都得换掉
They'll have to change all the filters,
可能得关闭好几周呢
probably shut it down for weeks.
你说得对  打电话给管理处吧
You were right. Go ahead, call Building Services.
-就说是我的错  -不  我俩都有错
- Tell them it was my fault. - No, we're both to blame.
这次就让我承担吧
You know, let me take the heat on this one.
好吧  别扯到我头上就行
Yeah, just leave me out of it.
如果他们进来看到满地便便
You know if they come here and see crap everywhere,
肯定马上怪在印度人头上
they're just gonna blame the Indian guy.
抱歉  我们还在实验室
Hey. I'm sorry, we're still here.
你那里还好吧
Is everything okay?
有点无聊
It's kind of boring.
虽然艾米误吸进一个羊毛球时
Although it did get exciting for a minute
我稍微开心了一分钟
when Amy inhaled a wool ball.
你们还要多久才能来啊
How much longer do you think you'll be?
我不知道
I don't know.
又进来了一只鸟
There's still a bird in here.
我们这下麻烦大了
We are gonna get in a ton of trouble.
亲爱的  今天是圣诞节前夜
Honey, it's Christmas Eve.
谁会知道你们在那里
Who even knows you're in there?
我们在签到表上签名
No, our names are on the sign-in sheet.
那就把名字擦掉走人呗
So erase them and walk out.
我可不能这么做
I can't do that.
不能做什么
Can't do what?
她叫我们把名字擦掉直接走人
She says take our names off the sign-in sheet and leave.
-我们可不能这么做  -对啊
- We can't do that. - Yeah.
* 叮叮当  叮叮当  铃儿响叮当 *
* Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way *
* 我们滑雪多快乐 *
* Oh, what fun it is to ride *
* 我们坐在雪橇上 *
* in a one-horse open sleigh, hey! *
艾米  这果干布丁真好吃
Amy, that pudding was delicious.
如果你喜欢葡萄干的话
If you like raisins.
多谢  我放的是无花果干
Thank you. And it's figs.
如果是这样  那就变得"超美味"呢
Oh, in that case, it was pretty good.
你还好吧  你都没怎么吃鹅肉
You feeling okay? You hardly touched your goose.
闻起来太像冠蓝鸦了
It smelled too much like blue jay.
我帮你收拾吧
Can I help you clean up?
你用海姆力克法帮我咳出了羊毛球
Oh, you Heimliched a ball of wool out of me;
就不麻烦你了
you're good.
我们开始交换礼物吧
Uh, what do you say we exchange gifts?
谢尔顿  我们没带礼物啊
Oh, Sheldon, we didn't bring any.
我以为你讨厌交换礼物呢
I thought you hate giving gifts.
我是讨厌
Yeah, I do.
所以我才给艾米带了这个
Which is why I got Amy this.
你给我带了礼物吗
You got me something?
不  不止是礼物
Oh, not just something, no.
我这是用心挑选的  节日主题的
It's from the heart, it's holiday-themed,
收据被我吃了  所以你也没法退了
and I swallowed the gift receipt so you cannot return it.
看看你坐在圣诞老人腿上的样子
Look at you on Santa's lap.
真是太可爱了
That's so sweet.
那当然  这礼物可完美呢
Of course it is. It's the perfect gift.
你现在有什么感想
H-How are you feeling right now?
是否有罪恶感  悲哀感
Guilty? Sad?
宁愿自己是不过圣诞的犹太人吗
Wishing you were Jewish?
不  我非常喜欢
No, I love it.
真的吗
Oh, really?
那这个怎么样呢
Well, how about now?
我亲爱的艾米  节日快乐
Happy holidays to my dear Amy.
我希望你能珍惜这份礼物
I hope you treasure this
像我珍惜你那样
as much as I treasure you.
但是你都没为我准备礼物
And you got me nothing.
圣诞节被你毁了
Christmas is ruined.
我们再也不要提这件事了
Let's never speak of it again.
哇  这还真好玩
Well, this was fun.
其实呢
Actually,
我为你准备了一份礼物
I did get you something.
我们不是有协议吗
But what about our agreement?
可你也送了我礼物啊  给你
Well, you got me something. Here.
饼干吗
Cookies?
是你外婆的圣诞饼干哦
They're your Meemaw's Christmas cookies.
我给她打电话要了配方
I called and got the recipe.
这些饼干太好吃了
They're perfect.
和她的拥抱一样美好
It tastes like her hugs.
圣诞快乐  谢尔顿
Merry Christmas, Sheldon.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
你开心  我也开心
You're happy, I'm happy.
也许一个强调馈赠的节日并不是那么...
Well, maybe a holiday that's all about giving isn't so...
拿开你的脏爪
Get your hand out of that box!
好了
Okay.
下一个游戏叫做寻找热豆豆
The next game is called Hot Boiled Beans.
我猜也是
Of course it is.
选一个人离开房间
One person is sent out of the room
其他人留在里面藏起一个小玩意
while the others hide a small item.
然后对外面的人说
Then they invite the first person back by saying,
"晚餐已煮好  热豆加培根
"Hot boiled beans and bacon for supper,
快快进屋里  趁热找到它"
hurry up before it gets cold."
如果你们觉得这比汤姆·汉克斯感恩节好玩
If you people think this is better than Tom Hanks-giving,
我也是醉了
you're all crazy.